Of course
I know you're not satisfied
But business is like a battlefield
The process doesn't matter
A loss is a loss
Lewes
You're outmatched, just admit defeat
You can't even keep a treasure when you have one
You just don't have
the luck to be rich
You've already started production
What's with that reaction
Do you understand
what we're saying
So have you
started production
Of course
Once we got the formula
we worked through the night
Now the warehouse is full of stock
It will soon be
turned into cold hard cash
Then I'm relieved
Ms. Zoe is indeed cunning
but her judgment is poor
Who are you insulting
What do you mean by that
My in-laws left so suddenly
I didn't even have time
to tell them
the mix I prepared that day had problems
It contained
nitrofuran ingredients
According to the government's latest policy
they are strictly prohibited
You're lying to me, right